{
    "subject": "Clive_Barker",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Hellraiser",
    "human_readable": "Clive Barker created Hellraiser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6933314800262451,
            "question": "What is Clive Barker known for creating?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6434600949287415,
            "question": "Who created the horror franchise Hellraiser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4227012097835541,
            "question": "What year was the first Hellraiser film released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.386710524559021,
            "question": "Besides writing, what other creative work is Clive Barker known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35816940665245056,
            "question": "Is there a television series based on Hellraiser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35727980732917786,
            "question": "Name a famous creature from the Hellraiser franchise."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3387245237827301,
            "question": "What type of horror is Hellraiser associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3374153971672058,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in the Hellraiser franchise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29179808497428894,
            "question": "How many Hellraiser films have been made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23416638374328613,
            "question": "What impact has the Hellraiser franchise had on horror cinema?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Clive Barker created Hellraiser.",
            "html": "yago_26798_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How many Hellraiser films have been made?",
            "html": "yago_26798_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes explored in the Hellraiser franchise?",
            "html": "yago_26798_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of horror is Hellraiser associated with?",
            "html": "yago_26798_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26798_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Clive Barker is the creator of Hellraiser, and that he wrote and directed the film adaptation of his novella \"The Hellbound Heart\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Clive Barker is the creator of the Hellraiser franchise, which includes films, books, and comic books. This information supports the statement that Clive Barker created Hellraiser."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}